
var myFlashcards = [     {question:"processor configured to perform various functions is a means-plus-function limitation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/09/lakkala-mass-inst-of-tech-aristocrat.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>lakkala</b></span></a>'},{question:"word 'means' not included than rebuttable presumption that not means-plus-function limitation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/09/lakkala-mass-inst-of-tech-aristocrat.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>mass. inst. of tech.</b></span></a>'},{question:"written description must disclose algorithm if means-plus-function limitation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/09/lakkala-mass-inst-of-tech-aristocrat.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>aristocrat</b></span></a>'},{question:"computer-implemented 112(6) corresponding structure is algorithm ",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/10/medical-instrumentation-harris-b-braun.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>harris</b></span></a>'},{question:"corresponding structure in spec with clear linkage for 112(6)",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/10/medical-instrumentation-harris-b-braun.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>medical inst</b></span></a>'},{question:"corresponding structure only if spec or prosecution history clearly links or associates it. quid pro quo",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/10/medical-instrumentation-harris-b-braun.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>b. braun</b></span></a>'},{question:"differences between prior art and claimed invention invoke 103&#44; not 102",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/02/baxter-travenol-netmoneyin-atmel.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>NetMoneyIN</b></span></a>'},{question:"112(1) written description burden on examiner to present evidence why POSITA wouldn't recognize invention disclosed in claims",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/02/alton.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>alton</b></span></a>'},{question:"if amended material inherently in the original spec&#44; not new matter",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/02/koito.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>koito</b></span></a>'},{question:"a completely subjective construction of a term renders the term indefinite",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/03/datamize-nautilus-interval.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>datamize&#44; nautilus&#44; interval</b></span></a>'},{question:"combination not obvious if would render prior art unsatisfactory for its intended purpose.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/03/gordon-ariad-abbvie-rochester.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>gordon</b></span></a>'},{question:"for not enabling examiner has to show entails undue experimentation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/03/angstadt-vaeck-armbruster-marzocchi.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>angstadt&#44; vaeck</b></span></a>'},{question:"enabled unless reason to doubt objective truth of statements relied on for enabling support",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/03/angstadt-vaeck-armbruster-marzocchi.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>armbruster&#44; marzocchi</b></span></a>'},{question:"rejection based on speculative assumptions about meaning of claim should be a 112(2) not 103",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/03/steele.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>steele</b></span></a>'},{question:"patent drawings do not define precise proportions",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/03/net-moneyin-hockerson-halberstadt-alza.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>hockerson-halberstadt</b></span></a>'},{question:"112(1) If alternative elements are positively recited in spec&#44; they may be explicitly excluded in claims.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/03/johnson.html.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>johnson</b></span></a>'},{question:"trademark "Java" in claim not indefinite because 'Java' is a well-known and widely-used term",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/03/simpson-ofarrell.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>simpson&#44; o'farrell</b></span></a>'},{question:"under 112(2) reasonable precision is all that is required",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/03/packard-swinehart.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>packard</b></span></a>'},{question:"nothing wrong with defining something by what it does rather than what it is",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/03/packard-swinehart.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>swinehart</b></span></a>'},{question:"expert opinion app meets 112 not entitled any weight facts supporting spec complies with 112 are",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/05/chilowski-lindell.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>chilowski&#44; lindell</b></span></a>'},{question:"where POSITA would recognize both error and appropriate correction&#44; not new matter",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/05/oda-vizio.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>oda</b></span></a>'},{question:"The structure corresponding to the means for a computer implemented function must include the algorithm",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/06/aristocrat.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>aristocrat</b></span></a>'},{question:"inventor may assume POSITA already knows the art and begin at point where invention begins",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/06/keller-carnegie-webster-loom.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>carnegie&#44; webster loom</b></span></a>'},{question:"112(6) does not apply to a nonce word",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/06/lighting-world-rodriguez-wms.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>lighting world&#44; rodriguez</b></span></a>'},{question:"written desc requires desc of the invention&#44; not merely drawing fence around outer limits of genus",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/06/eli-lilly-ariad-hearing-nautilus.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>eli lilly&#44; ariad</b></span></a>'},{question:"not all terms of degree indefinite&#44; spec must provide some standard for measuring that degree",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/06/eli-lilly-ariad-hearing-nautilus.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>hearing&#44; nautilus</b></span></a>'},{question:"uncommon definition must be set out in spec to give POSITA notice",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/06/paulsen-intellicall-sasse-hoeksema.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>paulsen&#44; intellicall</b></span></a>'},{question:"unless reason to doubt objective truth of statements relied on spec is enabling",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/armbruster-marzocchi-angstadt-sullivan.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>armbruster&#44; marzocchi</b></span></a>'},{question:"have to inform those skilled in the art about the scope of the invention with reasonable certainty",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/sebek-patel-sjolund-interval.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>interval</b></span></a>'},{question:"indefinite if a claim amenable to two or more plausible claim constructions",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/miyazaki-packard.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>miyazaki&#44; packard</b></span></a>'},{question:"for 112(1) all that is req is spec demonstrates that inventor was in poss of the invention.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/enzo-edwards-carnegie.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>enzo&#44; edwards&#44; carnegie</b></span></a>'},{question:"112(2) 'particular[ity]' and 'distinct[ness]' indicates claims req to be cast in clear not ambiguous terms",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/packard.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>packard</b></span></a>'},{question:"the use of the word "means" requires a search for structure in the application at issue",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/10/avid.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>avid</b></span></a>'},{question:"best mode two things: subjective&#44; was there a best mode + objective&#44; did inventor conceal",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/12/bayer-wellman-engel.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>bayer&#44; wellman&#44; engel</b></span></a>'},{question:"in pharma "enablement requirement may be met by animal tests or in vitro data"",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/04/edwards.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>edwards</b></span></a>'},{question:"Negative claim limitations adeq. supported when spec. describes reason to exclude relevant information.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/04/soni-santarus.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>santauraus</b></span></a>'},{question:"a description of a single embodiment "does not entitle the inventor" to broad claims",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/05/atofina-lizardtech.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>lizardtech</b></span></a>'},{question:"for 102(e) provisional application must provide written description support for the claimed invention.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/05/giacomini-lockwood-jepson.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>giacomini</b></span></a>'},{question:"102(e) prov app must necessarily disclose patentee's device&#44; renders obvious is not sufficient",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/05/giacomini-lockwood-jepson.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>lockwood&#44; jepson</b></span></a>'},{question:"claiming antibodies with specific properties can result in 112(1) problem if not adequately described",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/centocor.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>centocor</b></span></a>'},{question:"pure functional claim limitations can't encompass structures not invented performing function",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/08/wright-halliburton-miyazaki.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>halliburton&#44; miyazaki</b></span></a>'},{question:"spec must teach full scope of invention without undue experimentation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/08/wright-halliburton-miyazaki.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>wright</b></span></a>'},{question:"mere abs. of lit. support for neg. limit. not a prima facie case for lack of adeq. desc. sup. under 112(1)",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/08/parks.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>parks</b></span></a>'},{question:"words&#44; structures&#44; diagrams&#44; formulas that fully set forth claimed invention satisfy writ. descrip.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/08/wilder-enzo-lockwood.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>enzo&#44; lockwood</b></span></a>'},{question:"fact spec desc only singl embod insuf to limit broad claim lang",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/09/santarus-bimeda-howmedica.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>santarus&#44; bimeda&#44; howmedica</b></span></a>'},{question:"scope of enablement is disclosed in the spec plus known to POSITA without undue experimentation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/09/natl-recovery-fisher.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>nat'l recovery</b></span></a>'},{question:"chemical reactions may be unpredictable&#44; enablement scope varies inversely with unpredictability degree",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/09/natl-recovery-fisher.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>fisher</b></span></a>'},{question:"nonprovisional entitled to benefit of provisional if described in manner that satisfies enablement req.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/09/ziegler.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>ziegler</b></span></a>'},{question:"While beauty is in the eye of the beholder&#44; a claim term&#44; to be definite&#44; requires an objective anchor.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/10/datamize.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>datamize</b></span></a>'},{question:"no written desc support for genus if (1) unpredict in perf (2) spec makes clear only specific species disc",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/bilstad-tronzo.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>tronzo</b></span></a>'},{question:"disclosure of species may be sufficient written description for later claimed genus including that species",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/bilstad-tronzo.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>bilstad</b></span></a>'},{question:"descrip requirement needs descrip of invention&#44; not indication of result one might achieve if one made it",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/minformation-taltech-wilder2.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>wilder2</b></span></a>'},{question:"Whether written description adequately supports claims is an issue of fact.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/ariad-curtis.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>curtis</b></span></a>'},{question:"disclosure must reasonably convey to POSITA inventor possessed claimed subject matter as of filing date",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/ariad-curtis.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>ariad</b></span></a>'},{question:"To benefit from prior filing date&#44; a provisional must provide adequate 112(1) written description",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/03/trading-tech-elan-pharm-donohue.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>trading tech.</b></span></a>'},{question:"pointing to fact that claim I reads on embodiments outside scope of description satisfied 112(1) burden",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/05/wertheim.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>wertheim</b></span></a>'},{question:"if literature provides genes and their nucleotide sequences 112(1) does not req. their recitation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/05/falco-gunter.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>falco-gunter</b></span></a>'},{question:"The enablement requirement is met if the description enables any mode of making and using the invention.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/07/engel.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>engel</b></span></a>'},{question:"written description req ensures right to exclude scope doesn't overreach inventor's contribution",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/07/ariad-rochester.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>ariad&#44; rochester</b></span></a>'},{question:"The scope of enablement is disclosed in spec plus what is known to POSITA w/o undue experimentation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/08/natl-recovery.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>nat'l recovery</b></span></a>'},{question:"spec describes invention that has certain undisclosed yet inherent properties&#44; serves as adequate writ desc",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/10/yeda.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>yeda</b></span></a>'},{question:"Tossing out the mere germ of an idea does not constitute enabling disclosure.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/11/natl-recovery-genentech.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>genentech</b></span></a>'},{question:"scope of enablement is disclosed in spec + what wld be known to POSITA w/o undue experimentation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/11/natl-recovery-genentech.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>nat'l recovery</b></span></a>'},{question:"[n]egative claim limitations adequately supported if spec describes reason to exclude limitation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/11/inphi-johnson.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>inphi&#44; johnson</b></span></a>'},{question:"applicant's obligation is to supply enabling disclosure without reliance on what others may publish after",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/12/hoch-glass.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>glass</b></span></a>'},{question:"That a modified gene could have been "envisioned" does not establish constructive reduction to practice",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/12/goeddel.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>goeddel</b></span></a>'},{question:"claim that recites both a system and a method is indefinite because cannot tell when infringement occurs",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/ipxl.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>IPXL</b></span></a>'},{question:"long-felt need and commercial success impact obviousness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/barbed-wire-cyclobenzaprine-tiffin.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>barbed wire&#44; cyclobenzaprine&#44; tiffin&#44; artsana&#44; murata</b></span></a>'},{question:"claims that require elaborate explanations extraneous to spec are indefinite",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/packard-phillips-hammack-cohn.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>hammack</b></span></a>'},{question:"claims must be cast in clear terms",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/packard-phillips-hammack-cohn.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>packard</b></span></a>'},{question:"spec single best guide to determining meaning of claims",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/packard-phillips-hammack-cohn.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Phillips</b></span></a>'},{question:"if abstract idea present in claim do limitations include "significantly more" when recited with abstract idea",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/alice.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>alice</b></span></a>'},{question:"whether 'substantially equal' is indefinite depends on spec",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/12/wrigley-seattle-box-planet-bingo.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>seattle box</b></span></a>'},{question:"can't mix statutory classes of invention: unsure if contributory infringement when buyer performs claimed method of use",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/12/ipxl-lyell.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>IPXL&#44; lyell</b></span></a>'},{question:"evidence of correlation for the results between different measuring techniques enough to overcome 112(2) indefiniteness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/12/takeda.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>takeda</b></span></a>'},{question:"whether or not something is similar to or substantially equal to relates to breadth not indefiniteness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/05/andrew-corp.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>andrew corp.</b></span></a>'},{question:"Claiming two statutory classes within a single claim renders the claim indefinite",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/ipxl-lyell.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>IPXL&#44; lyell</b></span></a>'},{question:"breadth is not indefiniteness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/johnson.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>johnson</b></span></a>'},{question:"for 112(2) do claims circumscribe particular area with reasonable degree of precision and particularity",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/08/moore.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>moore</b></span></a>'},{question:"112(2) requires spec to provide way to measure term of degree",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/08/halliburton-datamize-miyazaki.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>halliburton&#44; datamize&#44; miyazaki</b></span></a>'},{question:"no per se indefiniteness rules&#44; degree terms definite only if POSITA can determine from spec",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/09/exxon-research-jolly.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>exxon research&#44; jolly</b></span></a>'},{question:"112(2) claims inform POSITA of invention scope with reasonable certainty&#44; absolute precision unattainable.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/10/nautilus.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>nautilus</b></span></a>'},{question:"for 112(2) spec must allow POSITA to visualize or recognize identity of subject matter purportedly described",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/10/wright-enzo.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>enzo</b></span></a>'},{question:"The claimed subject matter need not be described "in haec verba" in spec in order to satisfy 112(2).",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/10/wright-enzo.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>wright</b></span></a>'},{question:"claim term depending solely on unrestrained&#44; subjective opinion of particular individual indefinite",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/ddr-holdings.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>DDR Holdings</b></span></a>'},{question:"claim limitations reciting intended use merely go to the breadth of the claim and not indefiniteness.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/01/miller.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>miller</b></span></a>'},{question:"claim reciting both system (or apparatus) and method of using that system (or apparatus) invalid under 112(2)",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/03/ipxl-katz-interactive-ultimatepointer.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>IPXL</b></span></a>'},{question:"Whether a claim is indefinite is an issue of law.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/05/credle.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>credle</b></span></a>'},{question:"if use word of degree must determine whether patent's spec provides some standard for measuring degree",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/06/tomtom-seattle-box.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>seattle box</b></span></a>'},{question:"breadth is not indefiniteness.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/07/smithkline-ultimax.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>smithkline</b></span></a>'},{question:"claim elements individually or ordered combination transform nature of claim into patent-eligiblility",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/07/alice-mayo.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>alice&#44; mayo</b></span></a>'},{question:"breadth is not indefiniteness provided skilled artisan reasonably apprised of the meaning of the claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/08/metabolite.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>metabolite</b></span></a>'},{question:"The claims&#44; when read in light of the specification&#44; must provide objective boundaries for POSITA.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/08/interval.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>interval</b></span></a>'},{question:"for 112(2) sufficient support if POSITA would understand bounds of the claim when read in light of spec",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/09/miles-labs.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>miles labs</b></span></a>'},{question:"Markush: compounds have common functional utility and substantial structural feature essential to utility",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/09/harnisch.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>harnisch</b></span></a>'},{question:"Claim language employing terms of degree definite where provides POSITA certainty in context of invention",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/09/interval.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>interval</b></span></a>'},{question:"Breadth is not indefiniteness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/09/robins-gardner.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>robins&#44; gardner</b></span></a>'},{question:"indefinite to recite the already seen&#44; then use func lang at exact point of novelty",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/11/halliburton-general-electric.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>halliburton&#44; general electric</b></span></a>'},{question:"terms of degree require some measure from a baseline",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/12/interval.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>interval</b></span></a>'},{question:"programming or structure associated with functional language must be present to meet claim limitation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/12/nomiya-typhoon-touch-vizio.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>typhoon touch&#44; vizio</b></span></a>'},{question:"112(6) prior art equivalence means perf. same function in substantially same way with same result",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/11/donaldson-kemco.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>donaldson&#44; kemco</b></span></a>'},{question:"fact that claimed compound may be encompassed by disclosed generic formula does not by itself render it obvious.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/12/baird-jones-merck-williamson.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>baird&#44; jones&#44; merck</b></span></a>'},{question:"should abandon 'strong' presumption limitation lacking the word 'means' not subject to 112(6)",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/08/enocean-williamson.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>enocean&#44; williamson</b></span></a>'},{question:"Module' is well-known nonce word that can operate as substitute for 'means' in the context of sec 112(f)",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/12/williamson.html"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>williamson</b></span></a>'},{question:"112(6): words of claim understood by POSITA to have sufficiently definite meaning as name for structure",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/03/williamson.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>williamson</b></span></a>'},{question:"wherein clause limits a process claim where clause gives "meaning and purpose to the manipulative steps"",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/07/griffin.html"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>griffin</b></span></a>'}
     ];
myFlashcards = document.getElementByClass("answer"), i, len = linkArray.length; for (i=0; i<len; i++){ myFlashcards.innerHTML += linkArray[i]; }  

